Guide to the New-York Historical Society Ephemera Collection 1800s-2021 PR 264
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: Ephemera albums
  - Album 3 (disbound), circa 1900's (Offsite-box 12)
    This album was a gift of Maureen Howard, 2010
- Series V: Erotic advertising cards
  Series V, Erotic advertising cards, includes loose paper cards advertising phone sex hotlines, adult establishments and the like. This material is extremely graphic. Photographer Andreas Feininger donated most of the items in Box 9 and 9A, including a dis-bound scrapbook of erotic advertisements. N-YHS staff collected some additional advertisement during the late 1980s and early 1990s. The material in box 10 was donated by the Schreyer family.
  - Erotic advertising cards, circa 1980's (Offsite-box 9)
  - Phone sex advertisement, circa 1980's (Offsite-box 9A, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook of erotic advertising cards (dis-bound), circa 1980's (Offsite-box 9A, Folder 2-4)
  - Articles on phone sex trade, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 9A, Folder 5)
  - Erotic advertising cards and flyers, circa 1980's (Offsite-box 10)